Mic Check Mic Check 1 2 1 2 I just ate a hot pocket now I'm gonna show you guys
Mic Check Mic Check 1 2 1 2 我只是 吃了一个 热口袋现在我要告诉你们
how to unpack very bowls you know that doesn't really rhyme but as I was saying in this video what I want to do is I
如何 打开 你知道的 碗 并没有真正 韵，但正如我说的 在这个 视频中我 想做的是我
want to show you guys how to take a list and unpack it in two separate variables all in one line a nice little shortcut
想展示你们如何 采取列表 并将其解压缩为两个单独的变量 所有这一切都是 一个很好的小捷径
that's definitely going to come in handy a lot so first let's go ahead and make a
这肯定会派上用场 很多 ，所以首先让我们继续 前进 ，使一
simple list so say that we have I don't know a store or maybe we're just buying
简单列表所以说我们没有 知道一家商店或者我们只是在购买
a bunch of stuff online and we want to keep track of the information of these
网上有很多东西 ，我们想要 跟踪 这些 信息
items so the first element we want to keep track of is when we bought it or
项目所以 我们 想要 的第一个 元素 跟踪 我们买的时候或者
when we sold it doesn't really matter just make any list with like three
我们卖的时候并不重要 只需制作 三个 列表
elements in it just an example now for the second one I'll put the name of the
其中的元素只是一个例子 第二个我把 名字了
item say we bought some bread gloves and the third one is how much did we spend
项目 说我们买了一些面包手套 第三个是我们 花 了多少 钱
on 851 now again this is that it doesn't really matter just make anything with
现在又在851，这 就是 它 没有 真的很重要
three elements in it and also if you guys don't know what bread gloves are
它中的三个元素， 如果你 伙计们不知道 面包手套是什么
Google them and look in Google Images probably the best invention ever so we
谷歌他们，看看谷歌图片 可能是 我们 最好的发明
already know that anytime you want to access any of these elements in the list
已经知道 你想 ， 任何时候 访问列表中的 任何这些 元素
what we can do is just type the name of the list and the position so since it
我们能做的就是输入名称 列表和位置，因为它
starts with zero this will print out they if we just run this so this prints
从零开始，这 将打印出来 他们如果我们只是运行这样打印
out the day we can also put in one item too now if we ever want to actually use
那天我们也可以放一个项目 如果我们 想要实际 使用， 现在也是如此
these later on sometimes putting item zero that can be kind of confusing
以后这些有时会把 项目 零 ，这可能是一种混乱
because you know it's really the date the day always comes first it's like
因为你知道这 真的是约会 这一天永远是第一位 的
we're making a program where the day always comes first so we would store
我们正在制作一个节目 永远是第一位的， 所以我们会存储
that in the day and then we store the other one in a named item one yada-yada
在那一天，然后我们存储 另一个在一个名为 yada-yada的项目中
and then third one okay this is already taken up a crap line of code and you
然后是第三个好的， 这已经是了 拿起一堆垃圾代码和你
know I don't want to clutter up my program so would it be cool if there is
知道我不想 弄乱 我的 程序 所以 如果有的话会很酷
a way that we could set each list element to a variable all in one line
我们 可以设置每个列表的方式 元素到一行中的变量
well you guys are in luck because there is indeed a way to do that so say that we have this list right here and we want
嗯，你们 好运，因为那里 的确是一个办法做到这一点这样说 我们有这个列表， 我们想要
to set each of these elements equal to a new variable name well all we have to do is this put all of your
设置这些 元件 的每 我们所有人都等于一个新的变量名 必须要做的就是把这一切都放在一边
variable names and separate them with a comma so date item price now what this
变量名称并用a分隔它们 逗号所以日期项目价格 现在是什么
is going to do is it's called unpacking a list in two variables so it's going to
将 要做的是它被称为拆包 两个变量中的列表， 所以它会 发生
set the first one equal to date the second one equal to item actually let's
设置第一个等于日期 第二个等于项目实际上让我们
change that the name and the third one equal to price so now later on we can
改变名称和第三个名称 等于价格， 所以现在我们可以
just do something like print name check this out it prints out the name of it it
只是做一些像打印名称检查 这一点， 它打印出 它的 名字 它
saves you like oh well it depends on how big your list is about a crap line of
拯救你好哦，这取决于如何 大你的名单是关于 一个垃圾线
code now the only other thing I want to point out is this whenever you unpack a list in two separate variables you have
代码现在是 我想要 的唯一的其他东西 指出这是当你解包 列出你 有 两个独立的变量
one rule that you have to follow make sure that the number of variables equals
你 必须 遵循化妆一个规则 确保变量的数量 等于
the number of items in your list so if you have a bunch of lists and they have
列表中 的项目 数量 ， 如果 你有一堆清单， 他们有
different amounts or their different lengths you can't really do this because
不同数量或 它们的 不同 长度你不能真正做到这一点， 因为
it would be consistent and I don't know maybe you forgot to jot down the name of
这将是一致的，我不 知道 也许你忘了记下这个名字
one thing it's going to throw an error at yeah so there actually is a way that
有一件事会 引发错误 是的，所以实际上有一种方式
you can get around this and I was going to show you in the next video but I might as well show you right now so
你可以绕过 这个而且我要去 在下一个视频中向您展示但 我 也许现在就 这样 告诉你
whenever you have a list in there all the exact same size then you can use
无论何时你都有一个清单 你 可以使用完全相同的大小
that method and it's going to work perfectly it's going to make your code real nice and clean but what if you have
那个方法，它会起作用 完美它会使你的 代码 真的很干净， 但如果你有
lists that you want to unpack in variables that are different sizes well we can't use that method but we can use
要解压缩的列表 变量尺寸不同以及 我们不能使用 那种方法，但我们可以使用
a new one using this new symbol called the star and that's above the a on your
一个新的使用 这个新符号 叫做 明星，那就 在你 的上面
keyboard so when would we want to use this well actually saw a cool example in this book called uh I think it was
键盘 所以 我们什么 时候 想 用 这实际上看到了一个很酷的 例子 这本书 叫做 呃我认为 是
called Python cookbook so if you guys ever want to check out a cool book with like I know it has a like bunch of cool
如果你们这些人 称为 Python食谱 曾经想看 看一本很酷的书 就像我知道它有一堆酷
little scripts check that out I think I bought it on Amazon so anyways whoever
小脚本检查出来我想我 无论如何，无论如何在亚马逊上购买它
wrote that book thank you for this next bit of code so what you can do is something like this say that you're a
写了那本书，谢谢你的 下一步 一点代码所以你能做的就是 像 这样说 ，你是一个
teacher and you gave your students a bunch of
老师， 你给了你的学生一个 一堆
quizzes now what you just had to do is you want to drop the first and the last
现在测验你 刚刚要做的事情 你想放弃第一个和 最后一个
quiz great grade and average the rest of the scores together so maybe one class
测验很好的成绩和平均其余的 分数在一起 所以也许一个班级
you teach has ten quizzes maybe the other class you teach has five quizzes
你教的 可能 有 十个小测验 你教的其他课程有五个小测验
so you have this program you want to make but the lists are going to be
所以你有这个 你想要的程序 制作，但列表将是
different links well what you can do is start making a function and we'll just
不同的链接你可以做的是 开始制作一个功能 ，我们只是
name this function drop arm first and last because we're going to drop the
首先命名此函数drop arm 最后因为我们要放弃了
first and last grades and we're going to average pretty much all the middle ones
第一个和最后的成绩 和我们要 平均几乎所有中间的
together to give their student the final grade so what we're going to do is we're
一起给他们的学生决赛 等级， 所以我们要做的就是我们
going to pass in grades in grades is going to be the list but instead of just
要 在成绩通过在等级是 将成为名单，而 不仅仅是
unpacking it into a set number of variables what we can do is this the first item in the list is going to be
将它解压缩到一定数量的 变量是什么，我们能做的就是这个 列表中的第一项将 是
stored in the variable first the middle elements in the lists are going to be
存储在 变量第一中间 列表中的元素将是
star middle and the last one is going to be stored and last now what this
明星中间，最后一个是 存储，现在持续这是什么
expression right here says is take the first item store it in first
这里的 表达 说是拿走了 第一项将其存储在第一位
take all of the items in the middle now it doesn't matter if the list is 10 elements long then it's going to store
现在拿走中间的所有物品 如果列表是10则无关紧要 元素很长，然后它将存储
the eight ones in the middle if the list is only three items long then it's going
如果列表 中间有八个 只有三个项目然后才会发生
to only store one grade in the middle this little star expression right here is variable I probably shouldn't use the
只在中间存储一个等级 这个小明星表达就在这里 变量我可能不应该 使用
word variable but um I don't know you guys know what I'm talking about
字变量但是我不认识你 伙计们知道我在说什么
so that's exactly what it's going to do so the middle is the entire list
所以这也正是 它会做 所以中间是整个清单
excluding the first and the last so now all we have to do is calculate
排除第一个 和最后一个 所以现在我们所要做的就是计算
the average and you already know how to calculate average we just do real quick
平均而且你已经知道如何 计算平均值 我们只是快速做
it's the sum of all of the items in the middle over the length and this is
这一切都 在 项目的总和 中间的长度，这 是
pretty much going to count how many items are in that list so now we can
几乎 要算多少 项目在该 列表 中， 所以现在我们可以
just do something like print average and check it out we'll call this function
只是做 印刷平均和 看看我们会调用这个函数
twice so you can see what I'm talking about so of course we need to pass it in
两次，所以你可以看到我在 说什么 当然，我们 需要传递它
some kind of list now for the first one I'll just give this student some test
某种列表现在是第一个 我只是给这个学生一些测试
grade 65 didn't too - good on the first one 76 98 like 54
65级也没有 - 好像第一个76 98喜欢54
tanked on that one and the last one you got a twenty one you must have known
坦克在那一个，最后 一个你 得到二十一你必须知道
that they were going to drop it so of course what this is going to do whenever we throw it in it's going to store 65
他们打算 放弃它 当然，这是什么要做 的事情，只要 我们把它扔进去存储65
and first 21 and last and we're pretty much just going to toss those out
第一个21和最后一个，我们很漂亮 很多 只是去 扔掉那些
because it's going to store all these in middle and the average of 76 98 and 54
因为它将存储所有 这些 中间和平均76 98和54
is 76 mm interesting now of course like I said it doesn't
是76毫米有趣 现在当然像我说的那样
matter how many items we have 50 for $65.99 88-78 if you run this it's going
我们有50件物品 $ 65.99 88-78如果你跑这个它会去
to do the same thing so that ladies and gentlemen is not only how we unpack a
做同样的事情， 让 女士们 ， 先生们不仅仅是我们如何打开包装的
list into variables but also how we can use the star expression to give our
列入变量，但也包括我们如何 使用星形表达给我们的
program a little more flexibility so thank you guys for watching um well
编程更灵活一点 谢谢你们好好 看
that's all I got to say nothing more my bed I'll see you next time
这就是我得无话可说 我 床上 我会看到你下一次